Margaret Bourke-White Papers
Margaret Bourke-White Papers
- Photographic equipment
  - Contents of small zippered leather carpet bag (Oversize 39)
    1 Carl Zeiss Jena Biotar 1:1.5 f=7.5 cm lens No. 3320918 (lens scratched) in brown soft leather case
    1 Nippon Kogaku lens No. 323360
    7 adapter rings
    2 Wratten series VIII yellow filters K1 and K2
    1 Soho wooden lens board
    Weston Master III Universal exposure meter, model No. 737, No. 2210794 in gray leather case (glass loose)
    1 Nippon Kogaku Nikkor Q C 1:3.5 f=13.5 cm. lens No. 257282
  - Black leather suitcase (Oversize 40)
  - Contents of black leather suitcase (Oversize 41)
    Flash bulbs, bulb holdes, electrical cords, etc.
  - Tripod attachment (Oversize 42)
  - Rubberized cloth (Oversize 42)
  - Cameras and camera equipment (Oversize 43)
    1 Nikon 35mm camera in half leather case, no. 6145141 C 1:4 f=2.8 cm lens no. 342402
    1 small leather case containing dark slides
    1 Canon model VT 35mm camera, No. 501257 with Canon 35mm f:1.8 lens No. 12895
    1 Kodak-Medalist camera with Kodak Ektar 100mm f:3.5 lens No. EE3739
  - Reflector for No. 3 Superflash (Oversize 44)
  - Leather camera case (Oversize 44)
  - Contents of leather camera case (Oversize 45)
    Synchro lens for a Speed Graphic camera, telephoto
    Xenar f:5.5 F 27 cm Jos Schneider & Co. Kreuznack No. 295838
    Carl Zeiss Jena Tessar 1:4.5 f=14.5cm lens No. 1745899 on Ilex No. 3 Acme Syncro mount #S101-31
    Kodak lens hood
    1 Canon lens 50mm f=1.8 No. 202135
    1 Ilex Paragon Telephoto 9 in. lens f:6.3 No. 9164
    Leather lens bag
    Electrical cords
    Lens adapter ring
    Black cardboard squares
    Tiffen and Kenka yellow filters in plastic cases
    1 Leica-Meter No. 36719
  - Camera case with "Camera, Aircraft Type F:8 15" stencilled on front, and contents (Oversize 46)
    1 Keystone Camera, Aircraft, Type F8, focal length 15 in., Contract No. N-288-S10913, Serial No. 3405
    Wollensak 15" f:5.6 telephoto lens No. 423878, 1 viewer in case's pocket along with key to case
  - Linhof camera D.B.P., APa No. 43808 (Oversize 47)
  - Bellows for Linhof camera (above) (Oversize 48)
  - Wooden frame for Linhof camera (above) (Oversize 49)
  - Unidentified piece of Linhof camera (above) (Oversize 50)
  - Graphic View camera (Oversize 51)
  - Leather shoulder bag with equipment related to Graphic View camera (Oversize 52)
    2 lens hoods, one with yellow filter, one with red filter
    1 small leather Kodak filter holder
    1 Kodak Retina 35-80 Optical Finder for Kodak Retina Iic and IIIc camera in original box
    1 black shoelace
    1 box of Wratten filters
    Assorted hoods and camrea parts
    1 Carl Zeiss Jena Goerz-Dagor 1:9 f=12.5cm lens (serial no. 2009032)
    1 Kodak lens hood box containing viewer and shutter pieces
  - Franklin President Dual film editor (Oversize 53)
  - Equipment related to film editor (above) (Oversize 54)
    Various adaptor rings strung on a rope
    1 Kodak Electric-Eye Remote flash unit
    1 J.H. Dallmeyer 9" Dallon telephoto lens No. 99979 (corroded)
    1 Carl Zeiss Jena Tessar 1:35 f=16.5cm lens No. 1903560 (corroded)
    1 Carl Zeiss Jena Goerz-Dagor 1:6.8 f=30cm No. 2075128 with "Fried. Krupp A. G. Essen" engraved on side (corroded)
    1 Hugo Meyer & Co., Gorlitz & New York wide angle Aristostigmat 1:6.3 foc. 4 in. lens No. 853289 (corroded)
    1 Schneider-Kreuznac Xenar f:3.5 F=12cm lens No. 1410094 on Compur mount No. A055841 (corroded)
  - Camera case (Oversize 55)
    Very poor condition, with corrosion
  - Graflex series D view camera (Oversize 56)
  - Black camera case "12 Life" stencilled on the front (Oversize 57)
  - Contents of black camera case "12 Life" (Oversize 58)
    1 Nikon camera Nippon Kogaku no. 6145898 with W-Nikkor C 1:4 f=2.5 cm lens no. 402979
    1 half of a camera case with "M. Bourke-White" stamped on underside
  - Contents of black camera case "12 Life" (cont.) (Oversize 59)
    Contains:
    1 R.O.C. View view camera (wooden) with Bausch & Lomb Rapid Rectilinear 4x5
  - Lens box, green velvet, 8 compartments (Oversize 60)
  - Contents of lens box (Oversize 61)
    6 lens mounts/shutter assemblies (5 Compur with no ID, 1 Compur ID# 258646)
    1 Bausch & Lomb Protar VII Focus 18 7/8 in. lens No. 3236941
    3 miscellaneous mounts
  - Black leather suitcase with "Margaret Bourke-White, New York" stencilled across the top (Oversize 62)
  - Soho Limited view camera with small plaque saying, "M.B.W. From C.E.M. with best wishes 1944" No. M3831 (Oversize 63)
  - Ilex lens, Ilex Paragon Anastegmat f:4.5 E F 51/2 in. series S lens No. 45468 (Oversize 63)
  - Deardorff view camera, 5x7, New 450 series (wooden) (Oversize 64)
  - Quick-Set Senior tripod (Oversize 65)
  - Amigo Motorial camera tripod No. 25832 (Oversize 66)
  - Wooden tripod (Oversize 67)
- Photographs, personal
  This series contains candid and formal photographs of Bourke-White, alone and with others, from childhood through the entirety of her professional career. Locations include MBW's home in Darien, her studio in the Chrysler Building, lecture/publicity tours, speaking engagements, colleges and universities, exhibits of her work, and on location for various jobs in Europe and elsewhere. Other individuals who appear include family, friends, colleagues, and individuals encountered while on assignment such as military personnel (US, German, Russian, Korean, and other). Some items have accompanying letters, captions, notes, or other material. Unless otherwise indicated, all photographs are black and white. An item-level inventory of this material is available in Excel form.
  - Family members, family homes, family friends, circa 1895-1920; Edward J. Bourke; MBW's mother and grandmother; Joseph, Minnie, Ruth and Roger White; MBW as infant, child, young woman; William and Helen May Abbott; Mrs. Don Wayland; class pictures; MBW with bow and arrow, in snake-charmer costume, swimming, with friends, holding baby robin; 12 folders (Box 313)
  - MBW with friends and family; formal portraits, circa 1915-1929; MBW holding baby robin, at bonfire, in boat, in boxing costume, shooting a rifle, with various pets; Roger, "Pat", Francois Archibald Gilfillian; professional portraits of MBW including by Stone & Luckey, Everett Chapman/Dey Studios, Gordon Conner, Bernice Abbot. Earl Leiter; Dr. John T. Robinson with prize-winning fish; MBW's first car; MBW with camera at Terminal Tower, around Cleveland, in Chrysler Building studio; 12 folders (Box 314)
  - MBW at work in Russia, New York, 1930-1934; train station, Chrysler Building studio, Dnieper Dam, Magnetogorsk, Soviet Consulate in New York with Consul Genera Tolokonski; industrial photocollages; Hilliard Wood (Nashville Banner), Lillian Gish, Fred Peel; formal portraits by Paul J. Woolff, Gordon Conner; Chrysler Building gargoyle; dress for Artists' Ball; 12 folders (Box 315)
  - MBW at work, traveling, with various people, 1933-1936; dress for Artists' Ball; Chrysler Building studio, including pet alligators; studio of Karl Brown; Pan Am Flying Clipper; speaking to students; aerial photography for TWA, Croswell Bowen, Ralph Morgan; Sidney Moritz; at trial of Bruno Richard Hauptmann (Lindbergh kidnapping); with Eddie Rickenbacker, Laura Ingalls, Carl Brown, Alfred Eisenstaedt, coal miners, Ann Harding, other Hollywood people; portrait of MBW inscribed "To Skinny from Kit"; with coal miners; on horseback; South America trip; portraits by W.F. Gerecke, Dudley Brumbach, Carl Van Vechten; Pan Am publicity; 13 folders (Box 316)
  - MBW at work, traveling, with various people, 1936-1938; Chrysler Building studio; Saunders, Brabazon; Arctic trip, "Aboard S.S. Distributor," Fort Norman; photos of MBW by Rex Norman, Herbert Faris, Arthur Siegel; "You Have Seen Their Faces trip?"; Hollywood, Busbee Berkeley, Frances Langford; seated in judge's chair; Sam Resnick, Frank Demonti; newsstand at Grand Central; MBW speaking to large group and being photographed; on assignment for Borden's; at Ak-Sar-Ben Ball; aboard ship for Europe; 13 folders (Box 317)
  - Eastern Europe, England, Middle East, honeymoon, 1938-1939; aboard ship for Europe; Eastern Europe; pony cart with Evie Roberts; Mayor Frank Hague; with Bessie Walker Calloway, Bill Mason (Atlanta, GA), Kay Cain, Buddy Colley, Broome county (NY) sheriff Earl Daniels, Wilson Hicks, Walter Graebner; photos of MBW taken by Rita McGill, George Angel, Herbert Faris; on assignment for Life (telephone company, paper mill); in England (Daily Mail, Eton); Marines at Fire Island; on camel with Bedouin troops; MBW and Erskine Caldwell on their honeymoon; 13 folders (Box 318)
  - Honeymoon, Middle East, North Africa, 1939-1940; MBW and Erskine Caldwell on their honeymoon; Egypt, North Africa; elections; various portraits with unique photo manipulation; Halsman, J. Hampton Atkinson, Jimmy Collins; 14 folders (Box 319)
  - New York, World's Fair, on assignment as war correspondent, 1940-1942; "Colten Photos" New York; with Adolph Dehn, Ed Stanley, Eleanor Roosevelt, Earl Leiter, William C. Chaplin; photos of MBW by George Maillard Kesslere, Arthur Siegel, Louise Lux, F.A. Cole; "Leon and Eddie's"; publicity shots of MBW; North Africa with troops; New York World's Fair, Paul P. Horney; birds in flight; Rose Nahabedian; Russia trip (Smolensk, Archangel,; "Town Meeting in the Air"; TWA plane, service desk; "Town Hall"; with Maester and Landau at Hotel Adolphus; Arnold Eagle (BBC); 'Shooting the Russian War' publicity for Simon & Schuster, NBC Radio; war damage; MBW in uniform, with Lee Miller, 97th Bomber Group, Gen. Atkinson; 13 folders (Box 320)
  - MBW on assignment as war correspondent, "Women in Industry", 1942-1943; MBW with 97th Bomber Group, 1st Fighter Group, 92nd Division, Red Cross workers, "Ask the Man" poster, soldiers, sailors; Peter in uniform; "The Valley of Decision"; publicity for Dodd Studio, Kingsville, TX; Frank Armstrong; participating in Mutual Radio Broadcast; climbing rope ladder on ship; Dick Hart, North Africa; MBW poolside at RKO pictures, with Hal McAldin; photos of MBW by Don Padilla (with photo equipment laid out on the bed), Henry Allen (wearing aviator's wings), Alfred Eisenstaedt; with General Alexander, Helen Heitt, German POWs, war damage, in uniform of U.S. Army Air Corps, having breakfast in bed, "Women in industry" exhibit; 15 folders (Box 321)
  - "Women in industry", war correspondent work, relaxing with friends, 1943-1945; MBW with cameras, wearing hardhat; photos of MBW by Katherine Pete, Henry Allen, Lee Miller, Alfred Eisenstaedt, Morris Wasserman, J.A. Millard; with Captain Marinelli, soldiers, brother Roger, Fred Sullivan (NBC Chicago), members of U.S. Army Signal Corps, Earl Leiter; Krupp mansion; Colby College, ME; "Fletch"; at typewriter, in bathing suit at her pool, inside with friends; 13 folders (Box 322)
  - India and Pakistan trip, including LIFE job #25256, 1945-1947; MBW with Earl J. Leiter; publicity for "The Town House"; Nehru, Jinnah, P.N. Sharma; India and Pakistan people, places; photos of MBW by Croswell Bowen, Sunil Jannah; MBW in sari; Waldorf Astoria hotel; relaxing with brother Roger at home; 14 folders (Box 323)
  - At home, Rutgers University honorary degree, speaking on India, 1947-1949; relaxing with brother Roger at home; photos of MBW by Joe McGuire, Eugene Smith (Cincinnati Post), Amador Packer, Thomas R. Cragg, Alfred Eisenstaedt, Frank Goddard, H. Vernon Davis, Paul R. Schell, Oswald Bach; at Oklahoma College for Women, Chickasha, OK; receiving honorary degree from Rutgers University, with Dwight Eisenhower; holding This Is Cleveland book; speaking to group from podium; Halfway to Freedom lecture/publicity tour; relaxing at home; 13 folders (Box 324)
  - At home, at work, with friends, 1949-1951; MBW at home (making coffee, at typewriter, in autumn woods); with Russ Winnie, O.R. Bach, Capt. Kramer (USAF), Nate Cherniak, friends at dinner, at beach, other locations; Alexander Schneider playing violin in MBW's yard; photos of MBW by Mildred Capron, Constance Stuart, Henry Rapisarda, Tommy Lark, Lisa Larsen, Roy Stevens; gold mine; with guests at exhibit of her work; at Tavern on the Green in New York City; speaking to Camera Club of New York; Morton Press; in and around airplane, helicopter, cargo plane; on vacation; 97th bomber group reunion; in U.S. Air Force "antiexposure suit"; at Goose Air Force Base; receiving honorary degree at University of Michigan; on set of tv show; at United Foundation Report luncheon; 13 foldes (Box 325)
  - Japan, Zonta International, at work/at home, Jesuits (LIFE job #39902), 1951-1953; helicopter flight; high altitude flight; with Air Force officials; photos of MBW by Willard Hatch, Lee Kyong Mo, Joe Engels, Don Rice; "Economy pest control"; at exhibit of her work; Japanese family, Tokyo riots; Zonta International speech, with Major and Mrs. Lester F. Titus, Monsignor Shanley; relaxing at home; with Ann Sothern and other stars at a pool party; at Union Pacific Resort; with Barbara Lewis and Grace Rogers at exhibit of her photographs; at steel plant; on assignment for Life with Jesuits; 13 folders (Box 326)
  - Relaxing at home; various events/trips, 1954-1958; photos of MBW by Sharon Elser, Joe Rosenthal, Bill Rose, Cecil Davis, Walter Danzan, Peter Stackpole, Jim Leo, Ben Mancuso, Alfred Eisenstaedt, P.T. Cole, Frank Altschul; Stevens College, Kappa Alph Mu Induction Ceremony; in fancy dress; aerial photography trip(s); 88th Infantry reunion with General Sloan; Florida trip scrapbook, Pahokee Glades Observer; holding chimpanzee; being filmed in her home for CBS's "Person to Person"; unidentified lecture tour(s); at exhibit of her work including "Fort Peck Dam"; contact sheets of Ansel Adams; Canadian Pacific Airlines photo; Lynn Stewart; 12 folders (Box 327)
  - Relaxing at home; first operation, 1958-1960; photos of MBW by Frank Altschul, Alfred Wertheimer, Alfred Eisenstaedt, Bill Ray, Walter Dazan, Les Barry; award presentation photojournalism conference; speaking to Chicago Advertising Federation; before/after first operation (hospital, recovery, physical therapy); with Alfred Eisenstaedt, Peter Stackpole, [unknown] McAvoy, Eli Wallach, Teresa Wright; working on script for "The Margaret Bourke-White Story"; with Aunt Gussie and Roger's family; 13 folders (Box 328)
  - Family; at home; second operation, 1960-1963; with Aunt Gussie, Roger White, Roger's family, Ruth White, pets; with Victor Keppler, Alfred Eisenstaedt; Life magazine "Maggie's back" party; photos of MBW by Alfred Eisenstaedt, Joseph Wershea, George Tenney, George Karas; physical therapy; Martha's Vineyard; publicity photo for "Portrait of Myself"; 12 folders (Box 329)
  - Family and friends; relaxing at home; at exhibit of her work, 1963-1970; with Roger White, Roger's family, Ruth White, pets; dinner at Hotel Roosevelt; photos of MBW by Edward A. Rogers, Richard Corriden, Arthur Greenspon, Ray Fisher, Sam Falk, George Karas; at exhibit of her work; autographing copies of "Portrait of Myself"; with Sean Callahan; MBW's home; with group of children, cats, Dalmatian; 14 folders (Box 330)
  - Family and friends, 1924-1925; 1932,; circa 1970; with George Karas, friends and family at Life offices; photos of MBW by Ralph Steiner; miscellaneous portraits of young MBW; with students at University of Michigan; Everett Chapman, MBW's first husband; MBW with RCA mural; 10 folders (Box 331)
  - At work; South America; Arctic, 1931-1937; 1943,; 1946; in Chrysler Building studio; photos of MBW by Lotte Eckener, W.F. Gerecke, others; in carriage with group; South America trip, coffee plantation, "Jay Rice"; Arctic trip, seaplane, copper mine, Imooyak[?] family; Canada; MGM Studios on set of "Gold is Where You Find It"; learning to spin at Gandhi colony; on beach, at typewriter, in flight stuit;; 12 folders (Box 332)
  - Publicity photos, Allied Headquarters, Russia, 1938-1949; in flight suit; photos of MBW by Louise Dahl-Wolfe, Margaret Crosby Schadt, others; MGM and RKO publicity photos; with General Carl A. Spaatz at Allied Headquarters; in war correspondent's uniform in front of map and her photography; signing autographs; photographing downed Nazi plane; Russia, various locations, with Red Army soldiers, tank; at home in yard; 14 folders (Box 333)
  - Home and yard, American Women of Acheivement Awards, on assignment in Korea and Japan, 1949-1958; home, yard, cats, garage; photos of MBW by Hezzog, Yale Joel, Richard Dean; doing aerial photography at Biggs Air Force Base; dangling from Navy helicopter; American Women of Acheivement Awards including Life magazine cake and MBW ice sculpture; with Korean soldiers; Japan, various; Life 20th Anniversary; baby birds in nest; 13 folders (Box 334)
  - Relaxing at home; first operation, 1958-1964; baby birds in nest; photos of MBW by Alfred Eisenstaedt, Bob Henriques, Sam Falk, Stuart Abbey; in hospital, physical therapy; with Alfred Eisenstaedt, Edward Steichen; "Norman and the twins on the road" (toddlers, various); relaxing at home alone and with friends Shikego and Norman Sasamori, Monica, others; 13 folders (Box 335)
  - Friends and family; on assignment; surgery, circa 1920; 1963-1970; relaxing at home alone and with friends Shikego and Norman Sasamori, Monica, others; photos of MBW by Stuart Abbey, Richard Corriden; at exhibition of her work; with Alexander Schneider; Roger White as young man, White family; Life photographic staff group picture; women in steel photo; miscellaneous (related to LIFE job #1255-15A); surgery, recovery, physical therapy; 13 folders (Box 336)
  - Surgery, at home with friends/family, with Caldwell, on assignment, surgery, recovery, physical therapy; at home with family, friends, pets; photos of MBW by Cornell Gallagher, others; on ship; on set of unidentified movie; with camera taking photos for "NBC Mural"; at typewriter; with Erskine Caldwell; having hair done; in war correspondent's uniform in various locations; Christmas Card at Cornell; MBW at various ages, some candid and some formal; 13 folders (Box 337)
  - Portraits, candid shots, miscellaneous, portraits of MBW at different ages, some candid; with Carl Carmer, Karl Johnson, Erskine Caldwell, children; at home with friends, family, pets (includes some mounted photos); miscellaneous at work; "MBW's favorite picture of herself"; "To my wife with love from Skinny"; print of pencil portrait; 12 folders (Box 338)
  - Portraits, candid shots, miscellaneous, Mountain range; crucifix in church; rocks and people by [creek]; MBW's passport photos at different ages; original pen and ink portrait of MBW and photo of drawing; [Bill Staples] on carpet with flash bulbs and plates; Bound Brook house; 10 folders (Box 339)
  - Portraits, publicity photos, family, 1924-1925; 1932-1933,; 1942,; 1951-1952,; 1968; photos of MBW by Richardson Cremer (signed by him), Yale Joel, Stuart Abbey, others; RKO publicity photos of MBW in uniform and other outfits; tea with officer; American Women of Acheivement Awards including Life magazine cake and MBW ice sculpture; Japan, various; at University of Michigan; Everett Chapman, MBW's first husband; with RCA mural, New York Times, Roger White and family, Life staff; print of pencil portrait; relaxing at home; 3 folders (Oversize 22)
  - MBW personal files [MBW], interpositives 18538-18709 (Box 369)
  - MBW personal files [MBW], interpositives 18710-19119 (Box 370)
  - MBW personal files [MBW], interpositives 19120-19354, includes FDX 19355 on same sheet as MBW 19353/19354; and FDX 19358 on same sheet as MBW 19341/19342 (Box 371)
- Photographs, professional
  The vast majority of this series consists of black and white prints, contact prints, and interpositives, with a few negatives and slides and a small amount of color material. Included here are Bourke-White's work for Fortune and other commercial clients; her work for LIFE magazine covering India, Japan, Russia, and World War II; and photographs related to several books. including You Have Seen Their Faces and American Jesuits. Unless otherwise indicated, all items are black and white. An item-level inventory of this material is available in Excel form.
  Please note that a given folder may contain more than one topic or job number. For example, the Chicago Opera House is filed in Box 131, Folders 5-8 and Columbia Gas and Electric is filed in Box 131, Folders 8-10. As a result, Folder 8 contains photographs relating to both.
  - Independent jobs
    Corporate clients of note in this subseries include Fortune Magazine, Goodyear, National Broadcasting Corporation (NBC), National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), Pan American Airways (Pan Am), and Transworld Airlines (TWA). Individual clients include portraits (Patrick Clyne, Sergei Eisenstein, Mrs. Fitelson and baby) as well as estates and gardens (H. W. Albers, Dr. Charles Briggs, Leonard Hanna).
    - Adirondack Camp (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Adams, Biston, estate [ADA], interpositives 3041-3042 (Box 340)
    - Advertisers Inc. [ADV], interpositives 3043-3051 (Box 340)
    - Albers, H.W. [ALB], 1929 (Box 110, Folder 1-12)
    - Albers, H.W. [ALB], interpositives 3052-3192 (Box 340)
    - Aluminum Company of America [ALC], [1934] (Box 111, Folder 2-11)
    - Aluminum Company of America [ALC], [1934] (Oversize 1, Folder 1)
    - Aluminum Company of America [ALC], [1934] (Box 112, Folder 1-10)
    - Aluminum Company of America [ALC], [1934] (Box 113, Folder 1-11)
    - Aluminum Company of America [ALC], [1934] (Box 114, Folder 1-2)
    - Aluminum Company of America [ALC], interpositives 3312-3351 (Box 340)
    - Aluminum Company of America [ALC], interpositives 3352-3639 (Box 341)
    - Aluminum Company of America [ALC], interpositives 3640-3673 (Box 342)
    - Aluminum [ALU], interpositives 19719-19774, possibly more Aluminum Company of America (Box 342)
    - American Can Company (Box 110, Folder 12-13)
    - American Can Company (Oversize 1, Folder 1)
    - American Catalin Company [ACA] (Box 110, Folder 13-15)
    - American Catalin Company [ACA] (Box 111, Folder 1-2)
    - American Catalin Company [ACA], interpositives 3674-3758 (Box 340)
    - American Magazine [AMA], interpositives 3759-3764 (Box 342)
    - American Optical Company [AOP] (Box 114, Folder 2-8)
    - American Optical Company [AOP], interpositives 3765-3873 (Box 343)
    - American Smelting and Refining Company [ASR], 1929 (Box 114, Folder 8-12)
    - American Smelting and Refining Company [ASR], interpositives 3874-3880 (Box 343)
    - Amoskeag Mills [AMO], 1934 (Box 115, Folder 9-13)
    - Amoskeag Mills [AMO], 1934 (Box 116, Folder 1-6)
    - Amoskeag Mills [AMO], interpositives 3881-3987 (Box 342)
    - A.M. Andrews [AND], 1933; eggs, cigarette lighter, platinum products (Box 114, Folder 8-12)
    - A.M. Andrews [AND], 1933-1934; platinum products, Lektracase, children (Box 115, Folder 1-8)
    - A.M. Andrews [AND], interpositives 3988-4099 (Box 342)
    - A.M. Andrews [AND], interpositives 4100-4144 (Box 343)
    - Apparel Arts [APA], interpositives 4145-4157 (Box 343)
    - Armand Astringent [ARA], interpositives 4158-4168 (Box 343)
    - Atlantic Coast Fishery [ACF] (Box 116, Folder 6-7)
    - Atlantic Coast Fishery [ACF], interpositives 4169-4194 (Box 340)
    - Autos on Riverside Drive [ARD], interpositives 4195-4203 (Box 343)
    - Ayers and Company [AYC], interpositives 4204-4233 (Box 343)
    - Babe Ruth Statue [BAB], 1933 (Box 116, Folder 7-8)
    - Babe Ruth Statue [BAB], interpositives 4234-4253 (Box 343)
    - Badger, Mrs. [BAD], interpositives 4254-4261 (Box 343)
    - Bermuda [BER], 1932 (Box 116, Folder 9-12)
    - Bermuda [BER], 1932 (Box 117, Folder 1-2)
    - Bermuda [BER], interpositives 4285-4381 (Box 344)
    - Bethlehem Ship Building Corp. [BET], See Fortune: Bethlehem Ship Building Corp. [BET] below.
    - Blaker Agency, Hearst job [BAH], interpositives 9962-10035 (Box 343)